<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bryan Leung</string>
    <string name="firstLine">This is an app made by this beautiful specimen</string>
    <string name="aboutBryan">About</string>
    <string name="contactSocial">Contact me</string>
    <string name="placesVisited">Places I\'ve been</string>
    <string name="gamesPlayed">Games I play</string>
    <string name="playSnake">Play Snake</string>

    <string name="openingLineHome">This app was made to exercise my self-taught skills, practice clean code, and design patterns.</string>
    <string name="whatIWantToLearn">
        Implement APIs \n
        The many widgets Android offers\n
        Libraries\n
        Architectures\n
        To fully understand the Android life cycle and fragments\n
        The exception cases and how to get around them\n
        How to work remotely and get contract work\n
        To 100 percent all the free courses on codecademy so I learn basics of everything\n
        Fluency in Java and Python\n
    </string>
    <string name="dreamCompanyToWorkFor">
        \t\tI\'m looking for an opportunity where I can grow.
        Where my boss is respectable, knowledgeable, and well-communicated.
        A workplace where I am a valued asset.
        A company that invests in me and believes in my abilities.
        One that when I look back every year, I can notice my skills as a developer improve.
        A fine work and life balance plus great coworkers is the dream.
        Sends me off to conventions, conferences, hackathons, and work related events.
        Puts an emphasis on continued education and the latest tech.
        Has a few company and team bonding events.
        Tasty and healthy food.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutBryanBodyText">
        \t\tMy name is Bryan Leung.
        I am self taught and aspiring to become an Android Developer.
        I am a University of California, Santa Cruz graduate.
        I have a B.S. in Human Biology.
        After numerous years of science classes, hospital shadowing, internships, and medical work experience, I am making a career change out of science and health care.
        Now I am focusing on my quarter life crisis, which is a career change into the tech field.\n\n

        \t\tHow do I learn and what resources do I use?
        I use online resources to learn something everyday:
        Udacity, Udemy, Codecademy, Youtube, Blogs, Google/Android developer sites, Reddit, stackoverflow, etc.\n\n


        \t\tWhat am I doing while self teaching?
         I have filled the role of a stay at home mom but without the kid or the ring or the female role.
        Yes, that was supposed to be a joke.
        I meal prep for two, act as a six-star personal driver, and take care of highly dependent woman, who is getting her doctorate degree.
        I worked since high school and still have the student work permit to prove my early work ethic.
        I have had numerous other jobs since, mostly in food or customer service to help pay for college.\n\n

         \t\tWith my free time and when I am not studying, I indulge in my hobbies.
        I play PC games with my friends. I snowboard in the winter. I eat large proportioned meals.
        I slow cook ribs over hours and have meat that falls off the bone.
        After peaking at 230 pounds, I started exercising more and my goal is to stay sub 200s and healthy.
        I hike long distances for decent scenic views or for the Pokemon Go gyms.
        My personality or role is not static, but rather dynamic and versatile.
        I can be an introvert support in the back or the extrovert  head of the team.
        I am a great vacation planner as well as an open-minded and spontaneous person.
        I prefer clean and tidy but will get my hands dirty to do some manual labor if need be.
        I enjoy learning about mostly everything: politics, tech, science, the economy, current events, and local issues.\n\n

        \t\tDuring college I had many internships in the fields of construction, public health, medical, and education.
        After college I had a job at IHSS, now knows as Homebridge, working as a caregiver.
        I looked after many clients with many different ailments, physical and mental.
        While working, I volunteered, shadowed a orthopedic surgeon, and studied for the MCAT.
        I applied to medical school but am not pursuing that path anymore.
        Looking back, I know that I went in for the wrong reasons and I believe others do deserved it more.
        I am grateful for the many dozens of people who have helped me.
        My volunteer experiences vary from animal shelters, tutoring, and wildlife restoration.
        I paid off my student loans and have no debt.
        I also traveled to a few countries, attended weddings, and spent a few months with my ailing grandpa in China.\n\n

        \t\tThe bottom of each section will describe major parts and concepts of Android that I have implemented.
        As a reminder, this is one of my first personal apps and I am constantly learning.
        Thank you.\n\n

        \t\tThis page covers scroll view and nice string aesthetics.
        And because the home activity did not have this bottom description, due to design reasons, I will list it here.
        The home page covers Linear and Relative Layouts as well as onClick() buttons.
        I also show my use of clean code and practiced it in the XML values folder: colors, styles, strings.
        I kept hardcoding to a minimum and I have registered an id for all the views so that methods can act or call them.
        There is also a little welcome toast message that pops up when the app boots up. If you found this app through the Google play store,
        then that means I have learned how to follow the guidelines and publish an app.\n
    </string>


    <string name="entertainingStory">
         \t\tI will now entertain you with a story and how I imagine my life plan:
        While learning Java and Android, I create this decent app that acts like an extremely personal profile page.
        You somehow stumble on this. You are reading this, it impresses you, you like me, and you find me ambitious and driven.
        You want to give me a chance.
        You get me started off with an internship or temporary job at your company.
        Months go by and no one has a problem with me.
        My performance is satisfactory and I am reliable.
        You agree that my personality is a perfect fit for the company culture.
        Now it is the nearing the end of my internship, I receive an offer.
        I start off as a junior developer and after a few years and an open position, a senior.
        More positions open up and that I am interested in.
        I get promoted to Team manager or an administration position.
        You have noticed my leadership skills and important inputs after several more years.
        Eventually I am on the board of the company.
        The project that I started on has grown exponentially.
        You retire and at that going away party, you find that I have bought you life time tickets to that thing you love.
        I now reveal to everyone at that party that I will be taking over as chief executive (insert letter).
        Everyone is happy and the company is a success all thanks to you and me.
        Wow that was a great and entertaining story huh?
        A bit dramatized but that makes it more fun which engages you.
        Do you know how hard it is these days to keep people reading?
        Lots of short attention spans, instant gratification behaviors, and lack of intractability in this text string,
        and I still have you hooked and reading =).
        The moral to this story is that I am a decent person and you are interested in me because no one reads this far down
        and is not wanting to see me.\n
    </string>
</resources>
